SNEHA AWASTHI

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Senior Software Engineer with 2+ years of experience in Front-End Development and Mainframe DevOps. Had completed Bachelor of Computer Application in 2016. Looking forward for opportunities in the Data Analyst or PMO Analyst related field.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Capgemini, India, September 2016 - Present

- Trained on Mainframe technology for 3 months and worked on Batch Jobs and also on various tools of IBM such as IDz and z/OS Connect EE as a part of POC.
- Was also involved in the UI development part which included the use of Web technologies like HTML, CSS, Javascript and API connectivity for the same Project.
- Contributed towards coding batch scripts for easing the file transfers and other basic functionalities between Mainframe and Windows and also used excel macros along with VBA for automation purpose.

BETA TESTER (INTERNSHIP)

Frapp (Mobile Application), May 2016 - May 2016

• Beta Tested their application for various bugs and reported them whenever found one.

SUMMER INTERNSHIP

MMTC Limited, Mumbai, May 2015 - June 2015

- Studied the ERP system of the Organization.
- Minor contribution towards migrating MS FoxPro application to VB.Net.

- Snehaa2104@gmail.com
- 9820065516
- Mumbai, India
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/snehaa2104/

EDUCATION

B.C.A., 2016
IMED, Pune
Bharati Vidyapeeth
University,Pune
Percentage: 78%

XII, 2013 Mithibai College, Mumbai Maharashtra State Board Percentage: 61%

X, 2011 Lokhandwala Foundation School, Mumbai ICSE

Percentage: 87%

SKILLS

WEB TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5, CSS3, Javascipt, AJAX, Jquery, Bootstrap, SASS.

EXCEL SKILLS

• VLOOKUP, Pivot Table, Formulas, Charting.

DIGITAL MARKETING SKILLS

• Google Analytics

TOOLS & PACKAGES

• GIT, JENKINS, MS OFFICE.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

• Basic Python, Excel Macros, Batch Scripting.

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Analytics for Beginners Google, 2018

Certification in DB2 9 Fundamentals

IBM, 2017

Certification in Cyber Security

Intelligent Quotient System Pvt. Ltd., 2014

STRENGTHS

Good communication

Good Interpersonal skills

Persistent

Problem Solving

Adaptability

Critical Thinking

Handling Pressure

Leadership

AWARDS

Teck Rookie Award Capgemini 2018